piqora.com 2017-08-14

# Privacy Policy - Olapic | Visual Commerce & Marketing Platform

This privacy policy applies to [ _www.olapic.com_](http://www.olapic.com/) and [ _www.photorank.me_](http://www.photorank.me/) (individually and collectively, the “Site”) operated by Olapic, Inc., a Delaware corporation, and its subsidiaries (collectively, “Olapic”). The privacy policy also applies to the Olapic Platform (“Platform”) and the content management services (collectively, the “Services”) provided to customers who have engaged Olapic (“Customers”). This privacy policy describes how Olapic collects and uses the Personal Information (described below) you provide on the Site or through the Services, including through our mobile application. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your Personal Information and how you can access and update this information. By accessing the Site or using the Services, you agree to the data practices in this privacy policy. The use of the Olapic Site or Services and any Personal Information you provide on the Site or Services is and remains subject to this privacy policy and our Content Upload Terms of Use.

If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at <https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>.

CHANGES TO THIS POLICY

We may update this privacy policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by means of a prominent notice on the Site or Services prior to the change becoming effective. If you are an Olapic Customer, we may notify you by email (sent to the email address specified in a Customer’s account). Any access or use of the Site or Services by you after such notice shall be deemed to constitute acceptance by you of such changes, modifications or additions. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. If you do not agree to abide by these practices or any future privacy policy, please do not use or access the Site or Services.

PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT

We collect Personal Information from prospective and current Customers and, on behalf of our Customers, from individuals (“End Users”) who (i) upload user-generated content to Customer digital properties (such as a Customer’s website), (ii) use Customer hashtags or branded location tags on their social media posts, or (iii) interact with the user galleries and then buy product directly from a Customer digital property.

_Prospective and Current_ _Customers_ : We may collect information such as your name, email address and phone number and information regarding your social media accounts.

You can connect your social media accounts, such as Facebook, to your Olapic account. Those social media services will authenticate your identity your activities and sharing on third party social media sites are governed by each social media site’s privacy policies. If you leave the Olapic Site, you should make sure to read the social media sites’ privacy policies.

_End Users_ : We may collect information from End Users such as public uploads and posts, including publicly posted photographs, social media username, caption information (if any) and location tag information (if any). When End Users upload user-generated content directly to a Customer digital property, Olapic may collect your name or username and email address, prior to the upload, as well as your photo. When End Users interact with the user galleries and then buy products directly from a Customer digital property, Olapic may collect purchase information (including purchased product ID, transaction ID, transaction price, date of purchase, unique ID that our Customer may have assigned to you), email and username (if provided by End Users to Customers). Olapic does not collect information from private social media accounts or posts set to private but posted from public accounts.

We may also collect information from visitors to and users of our Site. As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data. We may combine automatically collected log information with other information we collect about End Users.

USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

_Prospective and Current Customers_ : We use the Personal Information we have collected from you to provide you with information about and access to our Services, to communicate with you about updates, maintenance, outages or other technical matters concerning our Services, to respond to your questions or inquiries regarding our Site or Services and to allow you to download information such as whitepapers.

_End Users_ : We only process Personal Information we collect from you to provide the services for which our Customers have engaged us. Our Customers use the information we collect in accordance with their own privacy policies. The Personal Information Olapic collects from End Users helps our Customers communicate with End Users regarding content that they have submitted through the Olapic Services. Furthermore, our Customers to whom you have submitted content through the Olapic Services or whose brand hashtags or branded location tags you have included in your social media posts, or whose products you have purchased from a Customer digital property after interacting with the user galleries on those digital properties, may use your username or email address to communicate with you, in addition to using your photo.

We may also use the information we collect automatically from End Users of our Site and Services to improve the Services we offer to our Customers, and to improve marketing, analytics and the functionality of the Services.

ACCESS TO PERSONAL INFORMATION

Upon request Olapic will provide you with information about whether we hold any of your Personal Information. If your Personal Information changes, or if you no longer desire to receive communications from us, or you cease to be an Olapic Customer, you may correct, update, delete or deactivate your information from our records by (for Customers) logging into your account and making the appropriate changes or emailing your Account Manager directly, or (for End Users) contacting Olapic at [privacy@olapic.com](mailto:privacy@olapic.com). We will respond to requests to access Personal Information under this paragraph within 30 days and provide you with the Personal Information we hold about you.

Olapic has no direct relationship with End Users. End Users who seek access, or who seek to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data should direct their query to the applicable Olapic Customer or contact us at [privacy@olapic.com](mailto:%20privacy@olapic.com).

CHOICE

_Prospective and Current Customers_ : You may tell us not to use your Personal Information (“opt out”): (i) for disclosure to third parties, except to a third party that is acting as an agent to perform tasks on our behalf and under our instructions (described in the “Sharing of Personal Information” paragraph below); (ii) for a purpose that is materially different from the purpose for which it was originally collected or that you authorized. To exercise your opt out preferences, please contact us at [_privacy@olapic.com_](mailto:privacy@olapic.com).

_End Users_ : If you are an End User and would no longer like to be contacted by those Customers on behalf of which Olapic has collected Personal Information about you, please contact those Customers directly. You may ask those Customers to delete your Personal Information and refrain from contacting you. You may also contact Olapic at [privacy@olapic.com](mailto:privacy@olapic.com).  If the Customer requests that Olapic remove the information from our records, we will respond to the Customer’s request within 30 business days.  If you do not want Olapic to collect your Personal Information from those social media websites from which we collect content, you can (i) update your privacy settings on those sites, or (ii) follow the opt-out process at the bottom of this page: <http://www.olapic.com/trust/>.

COOKIES AND TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES

Technologies such as cookies, beacons, tags, scripts or similar technologies are used by Olapic and our third-party marketing partners, affiliates, and analytics providers. These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the Site and Services, tracking users’ movements around the Site and Services, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by the third parties mentioned above on an individual as well as aggregated basis.

With respect to cookies in particular, we use cookies to analyze End User interactions with our Services and purchases on the digital properties of those Customers who have chosen to implement them _.  _End Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use the Services, but your ability to use some features or areas of our Services may be limited.

We partner with third parties to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partners may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on this Site and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out by clicking  _here_  (or if located in the European Union click  _here_ ). Please note this does not opt you out of being served ads. You will continue to receive generic ads.

FRAMING

Some of our Site pages, such as those listing job openings, utilize framing techniques to serve content to and from our partners while preserving the look and feel of our Site. Please be aware that you are providing your Personal Information to these third parties and not to olapic.com.

RETENTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

Olapic will retain Personal Information for as long as needed to provide the Services or as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

SHARING OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

We disclose Personal Information in the following circumstances:

  * To our Customers on whose behalf we have collected Personal Information from or about an End User.
  * To our affiliates and subsidiaries, including those located in the United Kingdom and in Argentina, to meet business operation needs.
  * To designated third parties to help us provide the Services, resolve or investigate abuse complaints, as described below. We restrict these service providers from making any use of your information other than to help us provide better service to you.

We may use third- party partners service providers to help operate the Site and deliver our features and Services, and may share your Personal Information with those service providers and other businesses involved in the normal operations of our business (such as website or database hosting companies, address list hosting companies, e-mail service providers, analytics companies, service providers such as companies which tag photos to products or otherwise analyze photos, job application processor partners, and other similar service providers that use such information on our behalf and under our instructions). When you sign up for our Services or provide information to us through the Site, we may share your Personal Information to those third party service providers only as necessary for the third party to provide the applicable service to us. These companies are contractually required to maintain the confidentiality of the information we share with them and to use your Personal Information  _only as necessary to provide  _these services to us.

  * When the information is related to spiders or bots, usually when investigating technical issues.
  * For abusive users, we may disclose information to assist in attempting to block the abusive user or to complain to that user’s Internet Service Provider.
  * If necessary to defend against legal claims.
  * When we deem it necessary to protect the property or rights of the user community, or this Site or the Services.
  * As required by law or to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process.
  * When we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request.
  * To any other third party with your prior consent to do so.

We will not sell, lease or give your Personal Information to third parties except as otherwise explicitly stated in this Policy or with your consent prior to doing so.

SECURING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

We employ administrative, physical and electronic measures designed to protect your information from unauthorized access.  Nonetheless, due to the inherent nature of the Internet as an open global communications vehicle, we make no guarantee as to the security of your information or that your information, during transmission through the Internet or while stored on our system or otherwise in our care, will be absolutely safe from intrusion by others, such as hackers. When you enter sensitive information (such as Customer log in credentials entered onto the Olapic dashboard), we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). If you contact us by email or a “contact us” or similar feature on the Site, you should be aware that your transmission might not be secure. A third party could view information you send by these methods in transit. If you have any questions regarding security you can contact us at  _privacy@olapic.com_.

We will make any legally or contractually required disclosures of any breach of the security, confidentiality, or integrity of your unencrypted electronically stored personal data to you via email or conspicuous posting on this Site in the most expedient time possible and without unreasonable delay, consistent with (i) the legitimate needs of law enforcement or (ii) any measures necessary to determine the scope of the breach and restore the reasonable integrity of the data system.

COMMUNICATIONS FROM OLAPIC

If you opt in to receive marketing communications from Olapic, subscribe to our newsletter(s) or become a Customer of our Services, we will use your name and email address to send communications to you. If you no longer wish to receive these communications you can follow the unsubscribe instructions contained in those emails or contact us at [ _support@olapic.com_](mailto:support@olapic.com).

We will send Customers communications about the functioning of our Services and similar service-related communications when it is necessary or useful to do so. For instance, if our Services are temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email. Generally, Customers may not opt-out of these communications. If you do not wish to receive these communications, you have the option to deactivate your account, or provide an alternative email address for contact by contacting us at [_privacy@olapic.com_](mailto:privacy@olapic.com).

SOCIAL MEDIA FEATURES

Our Site includes social media features, such as the Facebook “Like” button. These features may collect your IP address, information about which page you are visiting on our Site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on the Site. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the social media company providing them.

TESTIMONIALS

We may post Customer testimonials/comments/reviews on our Site which may contain personally identifiable information. We obtain the Customer’s consent prior to posting the testimonial if we include Personal Information, such as a name, of the Customer along with the testimonial. If you are the subject of a testimonial and want your testimonial removed, please contact us at [ _privacy@olapic.com_](mailto:privacy@olapic.com).

PUBLIC FORUMS

Our Web site offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at [support@olapic.com](mailto:%20support@olapic.com). In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why. Alternatively, if you used a third party application to post such information, you can remove it, by either logging into the said application and removing the information or by contacting the appropriate third party application.

PHISHING

It has become increasingly common for unauthorized individuals to send e-mail messages to consumers, purporting to represent a legitimate company such as a bank or on-line merchant, requesting that the consumer provide personal, often sensitive information. Sometimes, the domain name of the e-mail address from which the e-mail appears to have been sent, and the domain name of the web site requesting such information, appears to be the domain name of a legitimate, trusted company. In reality, such sensitive information is received by an unauthorized individual to be used for purposes of identity theft. This illegal activity is known as “phishing”. If you receive an e-mail or other correspondence requesting that you provide any sensitive information (including your password or credit card information) via e-mail or to a Web site that does not seem to be affiliated with Olapic, or that otherwise seems suspicious to you, please do not provide such information, and report such request to us at  _info@olapic.com_.

THIRD PARTY LINKS

Our Site or Services may contain links to third party websites. The fact that we link to a website is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party. We do not exercise control over third party websites. These other websites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personally identifiable information from you. If you submit Personal Information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. Other sites follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the personally identifiable information you submit to them. We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of the other websites you visit.

BUSINESS TRANSFER

In the event that Olapic is or substantially all of its assets are acquired by one or more third parties as a result of an acquisition, merger, sale, reorganization, consolidation or liquidation, such databases containing Personal Information may be one of the transferred assets. In the event of such a transfer, Olapic will place a prominent notice on our Site of any change in ownership or uses of your Personal Information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your Personal Information.

MOBILE APPLICATION

When you download our mobile application and use our Services, we automatically collect information on the type of device you use, operating system version, and system and performance information.

We do not ask for, access or track any location-based information from your mobile device at any time while downloading or using our mobile application and the Services.

We use mobile analytics software to allow us to better understand the functionality of our mobile software on your phone. This software may record information such as how often you use the application, the events that occur within the application, aggregated usage, performance data, and where the application was downloaded from. We do not link the information we store within the analytics software to any personally identifiable information you submit within the mobile application.

CHILDREN’S POLICY

The Olapic Site and Services are in no way directed to persons under the age of 18. Olapic collects Personal Information through third party social media services that are not directed at children under the age of 13.  If you have reason to believe that Olapic collected the information of an individual under 18, please contact us at [ _legal@olapic.com_](mailto:legal@olapic.com), and we will endeavor to delete that information and terminate the child’s information from our databases.

CONTACT US

If you have any questions or comments about this privacy policy or about our use of your Personal Information, please contact us at [ _privacy@olapic.com_](mailto:privacy@olapic.com) or you can contact us at:

**Olapic, Inc.  
Attn: Legal  
250 Vesey Street, 4th Floor  
New York, NY 10281  
Copyright 2017 Olapic, Inc. All rights reserved.**

This privacy policy is effective as of June 14th, 2017.
